wysada.com 2016-06-28

# Privacy Policy - WYSADA

**What information we collect:**   
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or Facebook profile. 

When ordering or registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, phone number or country. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

We implement Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising (e.g. Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Campaign Manager Integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.) 

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising. To prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, go to [Google Analytics opt-out page.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

We use data from Google's Internet-based advertising or third-party audience data (such as age, gender and interest) with Google Analytics. We, along with third-party vendors (including Google), use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookies) to report how your ad viewings and other interactions with these ads are related to visits to our website. 

You can read more about the cookies used by Google Analytics advertising features, by going to the [Google Analytics Privacy Policy page.](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

**What we use your information for:**   
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * • To personalize your experience: your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs
  * • To improve our website: We continually strive to improve our website based on the information and feedback we receive from you
  * • To improve customer service: Your information helps us to effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs
  * • To process transactions: Your information - whether public or private - will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason without your   
   consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested
  * • To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * • To send periodic emails: The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to   
   receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from Wysada emails, there is a "one click unsubscribe" button vailable at every Wysada email. 

**How we protect your information:**   
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information, when you place an order with us, or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database. This is only accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

**Do we use cookies?**   
A Cookie is a small data file that is stored by your Web browser on your computer.

We use Cookies to keep track of your current shopping session, to enable you to proceed to checkout at any time and to personalize your online experience. If you do not accept Cookies you will be unable to use this website. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**   
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties.   
This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.   
We may also release your information when we believe is appropriate. For example; to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, protect our property and safety, or to protect our rights and the rights of others. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Customer care**   
Please contact our Customer Care team during business hours for immediate assistance: 

**Our Address:**

Al Barsha1-Bedaya Building 3rd floor Office no.307   
Dubai, Dubai 487084   
UAE 

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post such changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, do get in touch using the information above. 

Wysada.com - Happiness Delivered
